(Raj:)Well, I guess it goes back to
(Raj:)when I was a fat kid in India,
and didn't have any friends.
(Bernadette:)I didn't know you were fat.
Yeah, I was 200 pounds
by the time I was in middle school.
(Raj:)Kids were mean.
Cows may be sacred there,
(Raj:)but it doesn't help
if you look like one.
(Raj:)Anyway, I was pretty lonely,
(Raj:)so I had to make up
my own stories and games,
(Raj:)and I promised myself
if I ever made any friends
(Raj:)that I would play
those games with them.
(Amy:)That is so sweet.
(Leonard:)I've seen old pictures of you.
(Leonard:)You were never a fat kid.
(Raj:)No, I was svelte as a gazelle.
(Raj:)A gazelle blessed with a flair
for storytelling.
I (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
(Bernadette:)Hey, what about this?
It locks like a receipt.
(Amy:)-What's it for?
-For a cup of coffee.
(Bernadette:)But it's dated 20 years from now.
(Raj:)From the future?
How fun and imaginative.
(Leonard:)So one of us came back from
the future to murder Stuart?
(Raj:)Correct.
(Leonard:)Does the gazelle with a flair
for storytelling
know he's ripping off Terminator?